A story about love at second sight.
While You Were Sleeping is a romance, comedy film directed by Jon Turteltaub.
A transit worker pulls commuter Peter off railway tracks after he's mugged, but—while he's in a
coma—his family mistakenly thinks she's Peter's fiancée, and she doesn't correct them.
Things get more complicated when she falls for his brother, who's
not quite sure that she's who she claims to be.
Lucy Eleanor Moderatz, played by Sandra Bullock.
Jack Callaghan, played by Bill Pullman.
Peter Callaghan, played by Peter Gallagher.
Ox Callaghan, played by Peter Boyle.
Saul, played by Jack Warden.
Elsie, played by Glynis Johns.
While You Were Sleeping is a 1995 American romantic comedy film
directed by Jon Turteltaub and written by Daniel G.
Sullivan and Fredric Lebow.
It stars Sandra Bullock as Lucy, a Chicago Transit Authority token collector, and
Bill Pullman as Jack, the brother of a man whose life she saves.
Other major cast members include Peter Gallagher as Peter, the man who is saved; Peter Boyle and Glynis
Johns as members of Peter's family; and Jack Warden as a long-time family friend and neighbor.
The film was a critical and commercial success,
grossing over $182 million worldwide.
Bullock and Pullman received praise for their performances.
Bullock also garnered a nomination for the Golden Globe Award for
Best Actress – Motion Picture Comedy or Musical.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois, coma, sibling
relationship, love of one's life, holiday.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.